A Charlie Brown Valentine is a family, animation,
romance film directed by Bill Melendez.
Lovesick Charlie Brown hopes – still – to get a valentine from the Little Red-Haired Girl, as
does Sally from Linus, Lucy from Schroeder and Peppermint Patty from Charlie Brown.
Charlie Brown (voice), played by Wesley Singerman.
Lucy Van Pelt (voice), played by Lauren Schaffel.
Linus Van Pelt (voice), played by Corey Padnos.
Peppermint Patty (voice), played by Emily Lalande.
Marcie (voice), played by Jessica D. Stone.
Sally (voice), played by Nicolette Little.
On September 10, 2025, Charlie Kirk, an American right-wing political activist, was assassinated at Utah Valley University in Orem, Utah, while
speaking at an outdoor campus debate planned by Turning Point USA, the conservative youth organization he co-founded and led.
Kirk, aged 31, was a close ally of US president Donald Trump and a
highly influential figure in the MAGA movement.
Shortly after the debate event began, with around 3,000 people in attendance, Kirk was fatally shot in the neck with a
single bullet by a gunman positioned on the roof of a building approximately 142 yards (130 m) away.
Kirk was taken to a local hospital, where he was later pronounced dead.
A manhunt for the shooter ended the following day when Tyler James Robinson, a
22-year-old from Washington, Utah, surrendered to the local sheriff.
Prosecutors charged Robinson with aggravated murder on September 16 and announced they
would seek the death penalty, alleging a politically motivated attack.
He has yet to enter a plea.
The assassination was highlighted as an instance of increasing political violence
within the United States and was condemned by national and foreign leaders.
Public reactions ranged from heartfelt messages expressing anguish
about the political climate to sharply partisan comments.
Trump, members of the Republican Party, and other conservative figures blamed members of the Democratic Party
and left-wing or liberal beliefs before a suspect was in custody or a motive was identified.
The Trump administration called for a crackdown against what it called "political extremism" on the left, which was widely criticized
by free speech advocates and legal experts as using the assassination as a pretext to silence political opposition.
A campaign by right-wing organizations and US government agencies resulted in mass firings and disciplinary actions against
people seen as celebrating Kirk's death or making critical comments about him in the aftermath of the assassination.
Kirk's memorial service was held at State Farm Stadium on September 21.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.